[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Because I'm nothing like her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "When people see you in the street, how many say -- percentage wise, just a rough guess -- how many say Phoebe and how many say Lisa?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "It's 50-50.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "And do you mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "I'm proud and you said warm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Did you become a lighter, warmer, cuddly person as a result of playing this character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I mean, definitely -- well, between Phoebe and the five other actors on the show, we were all really affectionate and warm and, you know, we just had a great relationship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Squillions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "How did making that program change you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, I think it -- in a -- in a few ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "I mean, what's the real Lisa Kudrow like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lisa Kudrow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Why do you think that you've been able to have such a sustainable and happy marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Because of the weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Because you're weird?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "I think it's the weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "And because your husband likes weirdness or tolerates weirdness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "I think he tolerates it, because he definitely -- he tolerates it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "How do you avoid the pitfalls, the cliches?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I come -- I mean, honestly, I think just commitment and thinking very far ahead, sometimes maybe too far ahead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "``", "NNPS", "''", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "At what -- at what stage of your \"Friends\"' mayhem did you meet your husband?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", ":", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "``", "NNPS", "''", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Oh, I met him just before -- I met him before \"Friends\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "So he lived the whole thing with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "To Vegas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "They don't go -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Would you allow that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Yes, I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Because you completely trust him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "I trust him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Did you find fame corrupting at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Did you -- did you go through periods when it affected the kind of person you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Is that part of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I do think that's part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Does that bother you or is it almost liberating that you had this incredible Mount Everest moment in your career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mount Everest"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Phoebe"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Everyone loved Phoebe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Don't you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Like a mascot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jennifer"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Jennifer missing out on that list?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Yes, I haven't talked to Jennifer in a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "So how long?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "It's been a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Do you, where you completely lose it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well, I mean I've raised a child so, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "He's -- how old is he now, 13?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "UDROW: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Uh-huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I've been through all the stages.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "And it is a fascinating thing to watch young men becoming men, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "So far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Does he watch it on television when it comes on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "He doesn't watch it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNS", ",", "''", "IN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "You're not cool enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "-- or \"The Simpsons,\" so -- no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Were they despairing of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Well, I wasn't on a sitcom for like eight or 10 years later.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "How intense were you before all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I think I was intense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "So you dyed your hair, what was your natural color?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Brown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "You were brown-haired?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "And then you died it blond and you immediately lightened up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I just started to gradually lighten up, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "With your biology hat on, what does this mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I think people treat you a little differently too when you're blonde.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Don't they think you're a bit more ditzy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "They might.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "So you learn more, ironically, because people view you as more stupid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "You're Camilla \"Boner\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan Bucatinsky"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Why did you come up with this thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Well, it was just -- you know, people kept asking my partner, Dan Bucatinsky, and I if we wanted to do a Web series.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Meryl Streep, I mean, goddess, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "In real life as big a goddess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "She's as nice as I assume she is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Do you crave big ratings again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "No, I crave enough ratings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No, no, I don't think I ever will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "I had the power to give you any five minutes of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "UDROW: OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Just having Meryl Streep do it, it's almost like the pope blessing you if you're a Catholic, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "That's exactly -- yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What has been the moment your mother was most proud of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I mean, recently there was a magazine cover and a great article about me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "And does your mom (INAUDIBLE) does she sort of run around the neighborhood (INAUDIBLE) making sure that they're all stocked up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Any women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Oh, so you're gay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "No, I'm not gay, I'm manly, but I'm not gay.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "How old are you now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "I'll be 42 in a couple of weeks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "You married a Brit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "But if you feel like you want to hit me, why don't you go ahead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "What do you really feel, warts and all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "You know, I can't believe I was that young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "I mean, how would you describe that process of going through the fame game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "Well, any time you're faced with fame on that level, it's -- it can be somewhat unnerving because you're never taught how to manage it and how to deal with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Do you desire that kind of hysteria again or are you just pleased it's behind you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "You know, I think everyone has their own individual experience.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richard Fitzpatrick", "Fitz"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "What is the premise of the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "The show is about Richard Fitzpatrick, the character that I play, Fitz.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fitz", "Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "So there's a touch of the Charlie Sheen sort of character, are we getting here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "Fitz, yes, Fitz is a bit of a Charlie Sheen kind of a character.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"], "LOCATION": ["Malibu"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Have you and Charlie ever caroused together on the town?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "Back in the day, you know, I used to go down to Charlie's house in Malibu.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "And was it all I imagined it would be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Do you stay in touch with any of them or does everyone just move on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "Well, a lot of us have moved on because at the end of the day we were all just people who worked together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Are you friends with any of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "Yes, with some of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "Where do you live now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "I live here in Los Angeles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Is there a culture to L.A., do you think, or is the culture just driven by the entertainment business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "It's absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "Have you found it brutal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2003", "2004"]}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "What has been the toughest moment for you personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "My toughest moments were maybe in 2003, 2004, after I had my big racing accident, I was really trying to get back on my feet after that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110805pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 812, "question": "When it happened, though, that big accident, did you fear that that might be the end for you in terms of your career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 813, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]